we've been given some code
and we need to fix the code so that it
will run correctly
so as a first step let's just run the
code as is
and you can see that an exception has
been raised
this is an argument error and the error
message tells us
that the wrong number of arguments has
been given to the dog
method we've given the method one
argument
but it was expecting zero let's take a
look
back at line nine of our code and take a
look at the problem
on line nine you can see that we've
passed the string
spot to the dog method however when we
look at our method definition on line 1
there's no parameter defined
on line 2 of the method you can see we
want to return the name
which in this case would be the string
spot so
we know we do need to define this
parameter for our method to function as
we would expect
we'll define a parameter name
and now the dog method is expecting one
argument
and receives one argument on line nine
so let's run the code again
we see the expected output regarding the
dog's name
however another exception has been
raised
and again this is an argument error
this time the exception has been raised
because of our code on line 10
and if we read the error message we can
see that the cat method
received the wrong number of arguments
in this case
the cat method was expecting one
argument
but it was given zero so again let's
revisit our code
on line 10 within the curly braces we've
invoked the cat method we didn't pass
any arguments to the cat method
but when we take a look at our cat
method definition on line five
you can see we defined a parameter
called name
and on line six we return name
so we do need that argument to be passed
in
let's pass in the string ginger
we'll run our code again and this time
we see the expected output
both of our methods are now working
without error
and that's because we've invoked both of
them with the appropriate number of
arguments now
so it's very important to always pay
attention to
how many arguments your method is
expecting
and make sure to provide the correct
number of arguments
to avoid raising an argument error